# Richard

### GATETE

#### Contact

Address:

Nyarugenge

Kigali-Rwanda

Phone:

+250788827485

Email:

gateterichad@gmail.com

#### Languages

Kinyarwanda – native English – fluent French – Beginner SWAHILI- BEGINNER

### Computer skills

Ms. Office (Word, excel and PowerPoint)

#### References

MUREKATETE

Tel. +250788270316

Nursing

SAFARI Innocent

Tel: +250789712320

Police

#### Summary

An energetic, friendly and competent person with s communication skills and a track record of experience in all s of the development cycle small and big institutions. Familiar marketing policies, learn quick and can cope with others ir complex situation.

## Skill Highlights

- Complex problem solver
- Team worker
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

#### Experience

2006-2012 government servant 2012-2022 Business man

#### Education

Jan 2013-2017 university of technology and art's of byumba (UTAB)

Jan 2004 – Nov 2007 | Advanced level secondary school - Groscolaire KIZIGURO

Jan 2001 – Nov 2003 | Ordinary level secondary school – Groscolaire KIZIGURO

Jan 1994 - Nov 2000 | Primary school - Groupe scolaire GAK